A Finding Aid to the Abraham Walkowitz Papers, 1904-1969, in the Archives of American Art AAA.walkabra
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, 1904-1958; Series 7; 0.9 Linear feet Box 2-5
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by George Lohr, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by Arnold Newman, 1943-1955 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by Yolla Niclas, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by Ruth Orkin, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by Roy Schatt, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by Marcia Stein, 1904-1909 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by Harry Teichlauf, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz and Alfredo Valente by Alfredo Valente, circa 1949-1957 (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by Carl Van Vechten, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by Clarence White, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
  - Photographs of Abraham Walkowitz by George Wiesner, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 5-7)
  - Photographs of Walkowitz with Friends and Colleagues, 1912-1941, undated (Box 4, Folder 8-10)
  - Photographs of Art Work by Walkowitz, circa 1904-1958 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Art Work by Others, circa 1904-1958 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Oversized Photographs of Walkowitz, Scanned with Box 2, F72, circa 1908-1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Photograph of Walkowitz by Arnold Newman, Scanned with Box 3, F16, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Photographs of Walkowitz by Roy Schatt, Scanned with Box 3, F19, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Photograph of Walkowitz by Carl Van Vechten, Scanned with Box 3, F25-26, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 3)